{
    "questions" :
    [   
        {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Calculate number of 1s in a binary number(num)",
        "answer":"num.split('0').join('').length",
        "options":["num.split('0').length","num.split('1').length","(num % 10).length","num.split('0').join('').length"],
        "level": 5
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "How to shift array elements to right in javascript",
            "answer":"arr.unshift.apply(arr, arr.splice(arr.length-1,1))",
            "options":["arr.concat(arr.splice(0,1))","arr.unshift.apply(arr, arr.splice(arr.length-1,1))","arr.push.apply(arr, arr.splice(0,1))","arr.concat(arr, arr.splice(arr.length-1,1))"],
            "level": 5
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "Why Redux saga is used?",
            "answer":"To make application side effects easier to handle and more efficient to execute",
            "options":["To support synchronous data flow only","It allows us to write HTML in React","To make application side effects easier to handle and more efficient to execute","It is a react life cycle method"],
            "level": 4
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "What does side effects mean in react",
            "answer":"A function is said to have side effect if it trys to modify anything outside its body",
            "options":["Side Effect is a react-specific term","A function is said to have side effect if it trys to modify anything outside its body","Side effect is a lifecycle method in Reactjs"],
            "level": 3
        },
        {
            "id": 5,
            "question": "What is 'Virtual-DOM' in React?",
            "answer":"Virtual DOM is an abstraction of the HTML DOM",
            "options":["Virtual DOM is an abstraction of the HTML DOM","Virtual DOM is virtual memory concept of OS","Virtual DOM is an data of the JSX","Virtual DOM is a built-in JS function"],
            "level": 3
        },
        {
            "id": 6,
            "question": "What is React.createClass?",
            "answer":"React.createClass allows us to generate component classes",
            "options":["React.createClass is a JavaScript Library","React.createClass is a sub method of useCallback hook","React.createClass allows us to write classes in hooks","React.createClass allows us to generate component classes"],
            "level": 2
        },
        {
            "id": 7,
            "question": "Presentational components in react are: ",
            "answer":"They are ‘stateless component’, for which a pure function can be used",
            "options":["Presentational components are components we present in JSX format","They are ‘stateless component’, for which a pure function can be used","Presentational components are components with state","Presentational components are simple JS function"],
            "level": 2
        },
        {
            "id": 8,
            "question": "How do you use hook in react?",
            "answer":"We import the useState Hook from React",
            "options":["Hook needs to install in React seperately","Hooks are built-in functions of react.createClass","Hooks can be downloaded from JavaScript IDE","We export the useState Hook from React","We import the useState Hook from React"],
            "level": 2
        },
        {
            "id": 9,
            "question": "Functional components in react are: ",
            "answer":"JS function",
            "options":["JSX code inside render function","react classes in a react component","constructor inside classes","JS function"],
            "level": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 10,
            "question": "What is react.js?",
            "answer":"JavaScript Library",
            "options":["JavaScript Library","JavaScript Framework","JavaScript IDE","Programming language","JSX code inside js file"],
            "level": 1
        }
    ]
}
  